hotschedules.com 2019-10-22

# HotSchedules Privacy Policy - HotSchedules

Last Updated: January 22, 2019

##  **INTRODUCTION**

This privacy policy (“Policy”) details the information we collect when you visit, access or use our websites and mobile applications (individually and collectively, the “Site”) and related products and services, including subscription services, developer platforms, premium services, plug-ins or any content or information provided as part of the Site (together with the Site, the “Services”). The Services include, without limitation, HotSchedules, Clarifi, Macromatix, GoHire, Manager’s Red Book, Digital Red Book, Schoox, Jobsabi, and Bodhi (each as applicable and together with its and their subsidiaries and corporate affiliates, “we,” “our” or “us”). This Policy also describes the purposes for which we use such information, the steps we take to protect that information, and your choices regarding such information.

## YOUR AGREEMENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

By accessing or otherwise using our Services, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy. You also understand and agree to be bound by the most current version of this Policy, which is the version then currently posted publicly at [http://www.hotschedules.com/privacy-policy/](https://www.hotschedules.com/privacy-policy/)

If you are using the Services on behalf of a company or other legal entity, you hereby represent and warrant that you have the authority to consent to this Policy on behalf of such company or other legal entity. To the extent this Policy conflicts with any existing agreement between the company or other legal entity you represent and us, this Policy shall control and supersede such other terms and conditions with regard to the subject matter of this Policy. Additionally, if you are using the Services on behalf of a company or other legal entity, you are nevertheless individually bound by this Policy even if your company has a separate agreement with us. As used in this Policy, “you” and “your” refer to you individually and the company on behalf of which you are agreeing to this Policy.

## OUR COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

 _Information that we collect from the Services_. Through your interaction with and use of the Services, we may collect information about you. The information we collect is either Personal Information or Non-Personal Information. “Personal Information” is information that can be used to identify you as a specific individual that we may collect through interactions with the Services such as your name, telephone number, physical address, or email address. “Non-Personal Information” includes information other than Personal Information that we receive through interactions with the Services including user browser and operating system, device type and other similar information, the other data you share with the Services, and Personal Information that has been anonymized or de-identified such that it does not identify a specific individual.

If you are a company or other legal entity that uses the Services (a “Subscriber”), we collect “Subscriber Data,” which is any data or information uploaded into or otherwise provided for processing by the Services by you or on your behalf. Subscriber Data may be comprised of Personal Information and Non-Personal Information and is used, stored, and shared in accordance with this Policy as applicable to all other types of Personal Information and Non-Personal Information.

In this Policy, we refer to Personal Information, Non-Personal Information and Subscriber Data generally as “Information” which may include any or all of these categories.

Information we collect through the Services may also include:

  * your e-mail marketing preferences;
  * information about your employer and your job function;
  * financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers;
  * information such as your nationality and country of residence;
  * information used to customize and facilitate your use of our Services, including login and technical information;
  * inquiries about and orders for our products and services;
  * information that assists us in identifying the products and services that best meet your requirements;
  * event registration information; and
  * feedback from you about our Services.

 _Information you provide to us._ If you use our Services, you may be required to provide us certain information. This may include:

  * information provided at the time of registering to use our Services, including our mobile apps, or posting material;
  * information provided when you report a problem with our Services;
  * records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us;
  * your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes;
  * details of transactions you carry out through our Services;
  * your search queries on our Site or through our Services; or
  * information obtained through your Facebook or other social network account if you register through Facebook and authorize us to access such information (e.g. work history).

 _Information that we collect automatically._ We collect Information about your visit to our Site and the usage of Services, including what pages you view, the number of bytes transferred, the links you click, the materials you access, and other actions taken. Within our Services you may be required to enter with a user ID, and we may connect this Information with your identity to determine your potential interests in our products and services. We also collect certain standard Information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and capabilities and language, your operating system, the date and time you access the Services, and the website from which you linked to our Site. The Information we collect automatically is statistical data and may or may not include Personal Information, but we may maintain it or associate it with Personal Information we collect in other ways or receive from third-parties. It helps us to improve and to deliver better and more personalized Services, including by enabling us to:

  * estimate our audience size and usage patterns;
  * expedite your search queries on our Services;
  * store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Site and Services according to your individual interests; and
  * recognize you when you return to our Services.

 _Information we already have about or from you._ If you, your employer, or your employees or other personnel or representatives have an existing relationship with us, we may already have Information about you, your employer or your employees that you have provided to us or we have otherwise obtained. In order to more efficiently and effectively provide the Services, notwithstanding any agreement you or the company or other legal entity you represent may have with us, you hereby authorize us to access and use such Information.

 _Your Address Book._  If you authorize us to do so, we may access data from your address book on your mobile or other device.

 _Geo-Location data._  If you authorize us to do so, we may collect information regarding your location through Google Maps or otherwise.

 _Information We Collect From Other Sources._  We may also collect Information about you from third parties, including but not limited to third-party verification services, credit bureaus, mailing list providers, and publicly available sources.

## OUR USE OF INFORMATION

Personal and Non-Personal Information may be used by us as follows:

 _Site and Services Use and Improvement._ We use your Information to deliver Services or carry out transactions you have requested. We may use your Information to facilitate our Site and Services in relation to our users, partners, advertisers, developers, and other websites. In order to offer you a more consistent experience in your interactions with us, Information collected by or through our Site or Services may be combined with information we collect by other means. We may use your Information to improve our Services or to make our Services easier to use by, for example, eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same data, customizing our Site or Services to your particular preference or interests, or suggesting connections based on shared work history

 _Communications._ We may use your Information to inform you or other users of products or services available from us. For example, if you inform us that you or your employee are no longer an employee at a certain company, we may send you, your employee, or other users information about other opportunities or the employee’s availability. When collecting Information that might be used to email you about our products and services, we will endeavor to give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such communications. Moreover, each e-mail communication we send includes an unsubscribe link allowing you to stop delivery of that type of communication. If you elect to unsubscribe, we will remove you from the relevant list within 10 business days.

IF YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO RECEIVE SMS (TEXT) MESSAGES, WE MAY SEND YOU INFORMATION RELATING TO THE SERVICES AND MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS (ADVERTISMENTS) FOR OUR SERVICES VIA SMS. IF YOU WISH TO OPT OUT OF SUCH MARKETING MESSAGES, REPLY TO SUCH MESSAGE WITH “STOP”. YOUR CONSENT TO RECEIVE SMS MESSAGES IS NOT REQUIRED TO UTILIZE THE SERVICES.

 _Employment Applications or Inquiries._ In connection with a job application or inquiry, you may provide us with Personal Information about yourself, such as a resume or curriculum vitae. In addition to other uses disclosed in this Policy, we may use this Personal Information for the purpose of employment consideration, availability, or otherwise for us, our customers, and other third parties.

 _Other Uses._ We may also use Information about you (i) to track and analyze trends and usage in connection with our Site or Services; (ii) to process and deliver contest and promotion entries and rewards; (iii) to protect our rights or property; (iv) to compare information for accuracy; (v) to verify your identity; (vi) to investigate and prevent fraud or other illegal activities; and (vii) for any other purpose disclosed to you in connection with our Site or Services.

Additionally, we use Information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including Personal Information:

  * to fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it;
  * to provide you with notices about your account/subscription, including expiration and renewal notices;
  * to carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection;
  * to notify you about changes to our Site and Services or any products or services we offer or provide though them;
  * to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences; or
  * in any other way we may describe when you provide the Information and for any other purpose with your consent.

We may use third-party service providers to process and store Personal Information and Non-Personal Information in the United States and other countries.

## DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Except as described below, Personal Information you provide to us will not be shared outside of HotSchedules and its parent companies, subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission.

 _Disclosure to Service Providers._  We contract with other companies to provide services on our behalf, such as hosting websites, sending out information, processing transactions, advertising, and analyzing our Site. We provide these companies with only those elements of your Personal Information they need to deliver those services. These companies and their employees are prohibited from using that Personal Information for any other purpose.

 _Disclosure to Partner Companies._ From time to time, we may seek your permission to share your Personal Information with certain partner companies for marketing purposes. However, we will not share your Personal Information for such marketing purposes unless we have obtained your express consent to do so. In addition, in responding to a request made by you, we may share your Personal Information with companies that integrate with, distribute or otherwise assist with or are involved with the Services. In those cases, we provide these companies with only those elements of your Personal Information they need to respond to your request, and these companies and their employees are prohibited from using that Personal Information for any other purpose.

 _Disclosure in Connection with Transactions._ In connection with certain transactions, we may disclose some or all of your Information to financial institutions, government entities, and shipping companies or postal services involved in fulfillment..

 _Disclosures in Connection with Acquisitions or Divestitures._  Circumstances may arise where for strategic or other business reasons we decide to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of Information to prospective or actual purchasers or receiving it from sellers. It is our practice to seek appropriate protection for Information in these types of transactions.

 _Disclosure through the Services._  Consistent with the purpose of the Services, we may disclose Information you provide to us to other users of the Services. As an example, we may share Information about you with your employees, employers, and co-workers for the purpose of facilitating the Services.

 _Disclosure for other reasons._ We may disclose Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal requirements or with legal process served on us, to protect and defend our rights or property, or in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of any individual. We may also disclose Information at your direction or to otherwise fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.

## THIRD-PARTY SITES & INTEGRATIONS

Our Site and Services may contain links to other sites such as our integration partners, distributors and sales affiliates, professional and government organizations, and publications. We also link to third-party providers that host, maintain and operate on-line training curricula. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by other sites.

Some third-party integrations with the Services may need to access or collect your Information, including Personal Information and Subscriber Data. If you choose to use these, we will share your Information with the integration partner to allow you to use the integration. We do not control integration partners’ use of your Information and their use of your Information will be in accordance with their own policies. If you do not want your Information to be shared with an integration partner, then you should not use the integration.

The Services may incorporate the Google Maps API. Accordingly, if applicable, by accessing or using our Services, you hereby agree to be bound by Google’s Privacy Policy (available at http://www.google.com/privacy.html).

## OUR USE OF COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS

Cookies are small files that websites save to your hard disk or to your browser’s memory. We may use them to track the number of times you have visited the Services, to track the number of visitors to the Services, to determine and analyze visitors’ use of our Services (including the effectiveness of online advertising), to store information that you provide such as your preferences, and to store technical information useful for your interactions with our Services. We may use session cookies (cookies that are deleted when your browser session ends) to store your user ID, elements of your user profile, to facilitate your movement around our Services (particularly in connection with information searches and order placement) and other information useful in administering the session. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies or to notify you when a cookie is being placed on your computer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the features of our Services or other websites that you visit. Our Services also may contain electronic images known as web beacons – sometimes called single-pixel gifs – that allow us to count the number of users who have visited those pages. We may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

## SECURITY

We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. These include physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards. For example, we store the Information you provide on computer systems with limited access that are located in facilities to which access is limited. For Services to which you login, it is your responsibility to ensure the security of your password and not to reveal this information to others.

## REVIEWING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

In some cases, you can review and correct Personal Information provided through our Site by going to the page on which you provided the information. In all cases, you can make a request to review and correct your Personal Information collected via our Services or ask that we stop using it by sending an email to customercare@hotschedules.com. We may take steps to verify your identity before providing you access to your Personal Information. You can help us to maintain the accuracy of your Personal Information by notifying us of any change to your mailing address, phone number, or e-mail address.

## CHILDREN’S INFORMATION

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act was created to protect children under the age of 13 from unsuspecting acts or practices in conjunction with collecting, using, and disclosing any information about them. Our Services are not intended for anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any Personal Information on or through our Services. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you are a parent or guardian or otherwise believe we might have any Personal Information from or about a child under 13, please contact us so that we can delete the child’s Personal Information. The Site and Services will never knowingly accept, collect, maintain or use any Personal Information from a child under the age of 13. If a child whom we know to be under the age of 13 sends Personal Information to us online, we will only use that Personal Information to respond directly to that child or notify parents.

## YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Site and Services that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to customercare@hotschedules.com or write us at: 6504 Bridge Point Parkway, Suite 425, Austin, TX 78730.

## ENFORCEMENT OF THIS POLICY

If you have questions regarding this Policy or our handling of your Personal Information, please contact us. We will promptly address your concern and strive to reach a satisfactory resolution.

## CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions, complaints, or claims, you may contact HotSchedules at 6504 Bridge Point Parkway, Suite 425, Austin, TX 78730, by phone at (512) 904-4299, or by e-mail at customercare@hotschedules.com.

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may occasionally update this Policy. When we do, we will revise the “last updated” date at the top and bottom of the Policy. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your acceptance of the then-effective Policy.

Last Updated: January 22, 2019
